razorsync.com 2019-06-29

# RazorSync Privacy Policy | Committed to Protecting Your Privacy

We operate several websites. It is our policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, we collect non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how visitors use our website. From time to time, we may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of our website.

We also collect potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. We do not use such information to identify our visitors, however, and we do not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that we use and disclose personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to our websites choose to interact with us in ways that require us to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that we gather depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who register to provide their name, email address, and company address. In each case, we collect such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with us. We do not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

We may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to our websites. For instance, we may monitor the most popular parts of the sites. We may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, we do not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

We disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to our employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf or to provide services available at our websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using our websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. We will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to our employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, we disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of ours, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of our website, you have the option to opt-in and we may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with and our products. If you would like to opt-out of such emails after you have selected to opt-in, please “unsubscribe” using the link provided within the email, or contact us at the address given at the end of this Privacy Policy. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. We take commercially reasonable measures to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies and Other Technologies

Our website, online services and email messages may use cookies and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. These technologies help us better understand user behavior and tell us which parts of our website people have visited.

We use cookies and other technologies to remember personal information when you use our website. Our goal is to make your experience with us more convenient and personal. For example, if you give us permission to send you, or you request an email on a specific topic, knowing your contact information helps us send you e-mail that is relevant to you.

If you want to disable cookies, check with your browser provider to find out how to disable cookies. Please note that certain features of our website will not be available if cookies are disabled.

As is true of most websites, we gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may use this information in marketing and advertising services.

In some of our email messages, we may use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination page on our website. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links in the email messages.

Pixel tags enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read, and they tell us whether mail has been opened. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to customers.

## Privacy Policy Changes

We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time, and in our sole discretion. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

### How You Can Update or Correct Your Personal Information

If you would like to update or correct any personal information in our records, please use the “update profile” link within the newsletter footer of the email (if provided), or contact us at the address given at the end of this Privacy Policy.

### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We do not share your personal information with third parties for direct marketing purposes. If that should change in the future, you will be provided with a cost-free means of preventing such disclosures of your personal information through an opt-in or opt-out process.

### Right to Lodge a Complaint (European Union)

Per Article 77 of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) / Datenschutz-Grundverordnung (DSGVO), you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular the Member State of your residence or place of work, or our company offices.

### Contact Information

RazorSync, LLC  
Attn: Marketing Department  
7725 Washington Avenue South  
Minneapolis, MN 55439  
U.S.A.

Telephone: (877) 675-4395  
Email: marketing@razorsync.com

**Effective Date: May 2018**
